I'm trying a [music] new Korean food
every day for seven days straight.
Told you [music]
I've lived in Korea for about 10 years,
but I was vegan pretty much the whole
time. That means I didn't eat meat,
seafood, or any dairy products. Even
kimchi usually isn't vegan. But now I
have no dietary restrictions, so I'm
ready to try some new foods. I made this
wheel to help me decide what to eat
every day. These are all foods that I've
never tried before. The food that I want
to try the most is definitely kamjatang.
I've heard it's delicious. The food that
I want to try the least is sanakji.
Hands down. The thought of eating
something that's still moving makes me
feel a little guilty. It's lunchtime, so
I'm going to spin the wheel and kick
this challenge off. I hope it's
something good. Ready?
go.
[laughter]
>> No way. Seriously, the universe hates
me, I guess. Do we really have to eat
this for lunch? [laughter]
I'm at Chagachi, Busan's biggest seafood
market. I used to be very adventurous
with food, but I'm actually so scared to
try San Naki. Not because of the taste,
but I'm scared it's going to suction to
my throat and I'm going to choke and
die. I'm really worried. Wish me luck,
guys.
>> Oh, it's going in the crack. Is that
okay?
I'm scared.
I googled how many people have died from
eating saki. Six people. I heard the key
is to chew a lot. They're all sticking
together. These are big pieces. Ain't no
way. Oh my god. I can't even grab it cuz
it's moving around. Oh my gosh. Do I
really got to do this? I'm so scared.
Why you shake your hair so much?
>> I'm going to chew like a hund times cuz
I'm paranoid.
>> 2,000 years later.
>> Okay, I'm sure it's good now.
>> Done.
I did it. I faced a fear today. It
tasted good. I think the cameraman
should try a piece. He's also never
tried sangaki, don't you think? Nope.
[laughter]
>> Is it okay? Whoa. Whoa.
>> Pretty good. Yeah.
>> Good job.
>> This is a prime example of don't knock
it till you try it. It actually is
really good. You just have to be
careful. Round two.
It's day two of trying new Korean foods.
Yesterday I said that I was most worried
about eating sangaki and I survived. I'm
still here. So I think today is going to
be a piece of cake. Ready?
[laughter]
Wow.
>> Okay. Let me [laughter] Okay. Yeah, for
sure.
>> Wow.
>> In the US, if you're hung over and you
have another drink the next day to get
rid of the hangover, we call it the hair
of the dog.
I'm going to get tipsy fast because I
have an empty stomach.
>> I'm using tongs to top [music] my soup
with green onion. I'm going to load it
up because I love green onion. All
right, let's just go for it. It looks a
bit spicy.
Oh, there's already rice in it. So, it's
kind of like gupba, maybe. Here we go.
Machin. It's very comforting and hearty.
I can see how this could cure a
hangover. Very delicious.
I have tried congealed pig's blood
before. It [music] wasn't my cup of tea,
but who knows? Let's try this again.
It's pretty bland, actually. It doesn't
taste like much. It kind of
disintegrates [music] in my mouth as
well.
>> This is better. It's not bad, but yeah,
I don't think I would ever willingly
order this. I would definitely order
this [music] again. It's day three and I
have a bone to pick with you. Why did
nobody tell me that it's jugi?
[laughter]
A friend just told me this last night. I
honestly thought it was gui. I'm so
embarrassed. Let me erase this and fix
it.
>> No, I like
Does it mean anything actually?
>> No. [laughter]
>> Okay, there we go. Jukumi. Jukumi. What
is my fate today?
Go, go, go. Oh, okay. Lotia. This is
actually [laughter] what did I spell it
wrong? Did I spell bud wrong?
>> Gay.
>> Okay. Okay. It sounds the same to me. K
G K G K G K G K G K G K G K G K G K G K.
I need to work on my spelling. I'm
actually really excited to try Loaria.
It's iconic here in Korea and they just
opened one in the US not too long ago as
well. So, let's see what the hype is all
about.
Ooh, they have a rice burger. I think
that's pretty unique. You would never
find this in the US. So, let's try that.
The shrimp burger, right? Maybe we
should do it as a set. Wo! You can
customize your bun. I'm going to get a
butter bun.
>> Is that the go-to?
>> It was 18,500
Korean one. It's pretty good bang for
your buck in the US these days. Even at
McDonald's, this would cost a lot more.
I always got to try the fries first.
M. It's very similar to McDonald's
fries, but it tastes like sour cream and
onion with this powder on it. Extra
points because it's fun to shake the
bag. And now for the main event, the
burgers. I'm going to start with the
shrimp burger. Ooh, this thing is
loaded. It's got lettuce and a bunch of
sauce. It [music] looks like tartar
sauce to me.
M. It kind of reminds me of a fish
fillet at McDonald's, which is my
favorite menu item in the US. So,
[music] I'm a big fan of this. Let's try
the rice burger. Now, when I was vegan,
I came here and ate a vegan burger that
they had, but I'm not sure if that
counts. So, this is my first real Loaria
experience. Wow.
It's got rice patties, a fried egg, and
some beef.
H. It's like handheld bib and bop. This
is okay, but I actually like real bib
and bop more.
It's day four and I'm ready for lunch.
So, let's spin the wheel.
Go, go, go. Oh, yay.
I've heard great things about gamatang,
so my expectations are set very high for
this one.
This looks so good. Cold noodles are my
favorite. Should I get this instead?
[music] It's so hot out today. Oo,
I'm wearing white today, so I need to
put on an apron. I don't want a stain on
my shirt.
They have some extra side dishes, but
they're self served. Let's go get some.
It smells so good. It's boiling right
now. I'm ladling some of the broth onto
the food.
>> You look so s
>> I don't want to drop it. All the hot
broth will splash on us. How do you even
eat this? Holy moly. That is a big hunk
of meat.
Wow. The meat is so tender. It just
falls off the bone.
M.
Dip it in the sauce.
It's like a mustard sauce. That is so
good. It tastes similar to a dish in the
US called pot roast. I'm not sure what
cut of meat pot roast is, but it tastes
similar. Try it with some kimchi.
M. This is delicious. I'm going to wash
it down with some icy cold macoli.
Oh, cameraman, did you order some
mabuku? What the heck? I told him not to
order this, but I don't know. I guess he
didn't listen to me. He insisted that we
get these. Was that believable?
[laughter]
M.
So refreshing. Actually, this is the
perfect combination. The spicy hot soup
with the cold refreshing noodles. No
notes. So good.
>> Don't say that. Culture tip. I know in
Korea it's kind of common to say, but
don't say that to a woman in the US.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I knew that was
coming. Out of everything I've tried so
far in this challenge, this is number
one for me. I'm mad that I'm just now
discovering gum to come after all these
years living in Korea. A little bit sad.
I [snorts] can't believe it's already
day five. Let's spin to see what I'll be
eating for dinner tonight.
Wa! Sundai. Oh my gosh. Okay, [snorts]
you can't have sund without. So, I
ordered yepto. I thought, why not kill
two birds with one stone here since
yepuck is also on the wheel. [snorts]
I've seen a lot of yeptuck mukbangs, and
that's why I'm wearing my pajamas and a
headband. I don't know why, but that's
what the mukbangers wear when they eat
this. Wo, that's a lot of cheese. This
is actually the main event tonight. This
definitely looks more appetizing in my
opinion, but who knows? I could be
wrong.
[music]
Here we go.
Not bad at all. Honestly,
it kind of tastes like a hot dog or
something.
>> Hot dog. [laughter]
It's a little bit mushy because of the
glass noodles, but I expected a stronger
taste. Let me try one more.
M. I like sund. Did not expect that.
Should I dig into the tapoki?
I don't know if that did anything, but I
tried hard for ASMR.
Woo! Wow! I think I chose the regular
spice level, but wow, my mouth is on
fire. The heat builds. At first, I
thought I was okay, but then it just
kept getting hotter and hotter.
Tastes good though. But wow, it has a
kick to it.
What is this?
I'm not okay. I thought I could handle
spicy food because I like kimchi,
sundubu, malatang. This is next level.
>> There were two more.
>> There were two more levels. How I
underestimated this. I always heard it
was spicy, but I didn't think it would
be this spicy. The cameraman has never
tried yepok either, which is crazy. But
come on, cameraman.
>> I don't like the pokei.
>> Yes, you do. You always steal a bite
when I have the pokei. Try. I challenge
you. Look who's in the hot seat now.
>> Haha.
>> Oh my god. I hate spicy food.
>> Wow.
>> How is it?
>> Wow. That thing is torturing. torture.
>> Tastes good.
Wow. I'm sweaty.
Wa wa. Pizza. Okay. I think that Korean
pizza is very unique because I've seen
pizza with toppings like bugi, corn,
sweet potato, and shrimp, which I've
never seen before in the US. And I think
this is a great chance to visit one of
Busousan's most famous restaurants, EJ
Mo. I hope there's not a long line.
Moment of truth. Let's see if there's a
wait. Waiting up. [cheering]
Oo. Luckily, we got seated right away,
but it's still packed. Let's order.
What's the most Korean thing on the menu
here? Oh, kimchi.
Okay, let's do this.
>> I love that they have fountain pop.
Extra points for that. And what's even
better is they have selfs served
pickles. I'm a certified pickle lover,
so I love that Koreans eat pickles with
their pizza. We don't do that in the US.
If we were to have a side with pizza in
the US, it would usually be salad or
bread sticks. Maybe chicken wings. I
wish we did this in the US. It balances
it so well. Wow.
Load it up. Wow. There's a lot going on
with this pizza. I can already see the
crust. It's a hot dog inside. I'm
excited to try something new. Ooh. And
in Korea, you use a fork and knife to
eat pizza usually, right?
Surprisingly, I don't taste the kimchi
too much. I'm so curious about this
sweet potato and hot dog crust. Okay,
here we go.
H I mean I do like hot dogs, so it
tastes good. This is kind of like a two
for one deal. You get a hot dog and
pizza. I didn't hate it, but I'll
probably stick to Detroit or New York
style pizza. Maybe I'm biased. This is
an over-the-top pizza.
This challenge flew by. It's already the
last day, so it's time to spin the wheel
and see what I'm going to eat for my
final dinner. It better be something
good.
Come on. Don't tell me that's bondi.
[music] Is it? Oh, no.
Bondi, I'll do it. Got to go out with
the bang anyways, you know. Got to Let's
go.
We can't find the bondi. Where is it?
>> You heard them. No bondi. Sorry, guys.
>> You can get it at the bar. Canned one.
>> Canned bondi. Wa. Um, that sounds even
worse. But okay. Sure. You're going to
try it with me?
>> No.
>> That's what I thought.
>> They have it. Low key. I was hoping they
didn't have it.
In English, it's silkworm pupa. This is
a big can. Do they have a smaller Oh,
they do have a smaller can. Let's do
this. I can feel them floating in here.
Wow. This is my final meal of the
challenge. Seriously.
Let's crack this open. Wow.
Woo. that has a strong smell to it. I
like a lot of stinky foods like cheese,
eggs, and fish. So, I'm staying
cautiously optimistic. Even though it's
a little smelly, maybe I'll like the
taste of it.
>> You're a trooper. [laughter]
>> You know what? It's not the first time
I've eaten an insect before. I ate
grasshoppers in Mexico. Hey,
don't think about it. Just do it [music]
down the hatch.
Not for me. I actually wanted to like
this because I heard it's good protein.
[laughter]
I have some water.
It tastes exactly how it smells, and
that's the only way I can describe it.
If you don't like something, but you
want to say it politely, or you don't
want to offend someone, you can say,
"It's not for me," or, "It's not my cup
of tea."
>> That's disgusting.
>> That's the end of the challenge. It was
[music] actually a lot of fun trying
different foods throughout the week.
[music] My favorite food that I tried
was definitely tang. My least favorite
food was bundi. Let me know in the
comments [music] what you think I should
try next. Bye.